<?xml version="1.0" encoding="US-ASCII"?>
<!DOCTYPE rfc SYSTEM "rfc2629.dtd" [

]>

<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='rfc2629.xslt' ?>

<?rfc strict="yes" ?>
<?rfc toc="yes"?>
<?rfc tocdepth="4"?>
<?rfc symrefs="yes"?>
<?rfc sortrefs="yes" ?>
<?rfc compact="yes" ?>
<?rfc subcompact="no" ?>
<rfc category="std" docName="draft-wibrown-office-card-protocol-00" ipr="trust200902">

<front>

    <title abbrev="Office Card Protocol">Office Card Protocol</title>


   <author fullname="William Brown" initials="W.B." surname="Brown">
     <organization>Blackhat Networks Australia</organization>

     <address>

       <phone></phone>

       <email>william@blackhats.net.au</email>

       <!-- uri and facsimile elements may also be added -->
     </address>
   </author>

   <date year="2018"></date>
   <workgroup>Internet Engineering Task Force</workgroup>

    <!-- I am not sure of the appropriate keywords here -->
   <keyword>draft-wibrown-office-card-protocol</keyword>

   <abstract>
        <t>In the modern workplace it is customary for employees to sign cards of well-wishes to associates who are
        departing or experiencing an emotional event (positive or negative). These cards are generally of large physical dimensions relative to
        cards given to others. The large size of these cards relates to the ability for the cards to hold numerous
        signatures and emotionally inspired messages to the associate. Creation of these signatures must be done in
        private so that the effect of the card can be fully realised for the recipient. Many institutes however have
        synchronisation issues with the signing and delivery of these cards. A protocol for card management is required
        to ensure that all signatures are delivered correctly to the recipient.
        </t>
   </abstract>
</front>

<middle>

    <section title="Card Terminology">
        <t>The Card. The card is a large piece of cardboard, generally with colourful artwork and a witty remark printed
        upon it's surface. The card contains ample white space which is used for notation of small feeling oriented messages.
        </t>
        <t>Card Receiver. This is the individual whom the Card is destined for. The Card Receiver MUST not be aware
        of the instantiation of the Office Card Protocol.
        </t>
        <t>Card Initiator. The Card Initiator is generally a person with a relationship to the Card Receiver. This individual
        believes a life event of signifgance has or will occur and initiates the Office Card Protocol. It is beyond the scope of this document to
        determine all possible scenarioes in which a card may be instaniated by the Card Initiator.
        </t>
        <t>Card Signing Party. A Card Signing Party is an individual who is requested to sign the the card. It is beyond
        the scope of this document to determine all office social relationships where a Card Signing Party MAY feel the
        requirment to sign the Card.
        </t>
    </section>

    <section title="Initialisation">
        <t>The Card Initiator determines an event is occuring related to the Card Receiver that warrants the creation of
        the Card. The Card Initiator SHOULD determine from their available budget an appropriate amount to spend on the
        acquisition of the Card. Additionally, the Card Initiator SHOULD choose a card with an appropriate emotional or
        comical artwork or text relevant to the situation experienced by the Card Receiver. It is beyond the scope
        of this document to discuss appropriate Card artworks or messages. We assume the Card Initiator has an appropriate
        relationship with the Card Receiver to make an informed decision on appropriate card content.
        </t>
        <t>The Card Initiator provides the original signature - The Card Initiator may also be a Card Signing Party.
        The Card Initiator MUST provide some form of temporary location pointer via a disposable text interface such as
        a "post it note" or "note paper" to allow returning of the Card from a Card Signing Party to the Card Initiator.
        </t>
        <t>The Card Initiator MUST identify a possible starting port for the Card into the network of Card Signing Parties.
        </t>
    </section>

    <section title="Card Signing Network Operations">
        <t>The Card Initiator delivers the card to a Card Signing Party. The Card Signing Party must make a series of decisions
        related to the Card.
        </t>
        <t>The Card Signing Party MUST choose if they have an appropriate relationship with the Card Receiver to issue a signature.
        If not relationship is determined the Card Signing Party omits a signature. If a relationship is found, a signature MAY be
        created. The content of the signature is dependent on many factors such as working relationship, length of relationship in time,
        friendship or more. Content of signatures is beyond the scope of this document. As signatures are public information only
        appropriate content MUST be signed.
        </t>
        <t>The Card Signing Party who physically holds the Card is always responsible for routing decisions. The Card Signing Party SHOULD
        communicate with other nearby potential Card Signing Parties for verification of routing oppurtunities. Card Signing Parties who have
        already signed the card MAY accept the Card to provide further routing into the Card Signing Network. A Card Signing Party who has NOT
        signed the Card always has a higher routing priority than a Card Signing Party who has previously signed the Card.
        </t>
        <t>As the Card is routed through the Card Signing Network, Card Signing Parties should take note of density of signatures and the
        potential network distance relative to the Card Initator. If the density becomes high, then further signatures MUST not be created, and
        the card MUST be returned the the Card Initator. If the Card Signing Party believes the distance of the Card from the Card Initiator
        is too high then the Card SHOULD be returned to the Card Initator.
        </t>
        <t>If a routing decision can not be reached, the card MUST be return via the address pointer to the Card Initator.
        </t>
        <t>The Card Initator may inspect the Card and determine that the signature density is insufficent and MAY reinsert the Card into the
        Card Signing Network at a different entry location (aka Card Signing Party). The Card Signing Party may indicate that they
        have already provided a signature and MAY reject the reinsertion. The Card Initator must then attempt a new reinsertion location.
        </t>
    </section>

    <section title="Delivery of The Card">
        <t>Once the Card Initator has determined the Card contains sufficent signature density they can cease the Card Signing Network
        operations.
        </t>
        <t>The Card MUST be presented to the Card Receiver. The Card presentation SHOULD be at an event appropriate to the nature of the
        card. It is beyond the scope of this document to determine appropriate presentation techniques or events.
        </t>
        <t>Once the Card is presented, the Card Receiver SHOULD read and validate all provided signatures. Once the Card Receiver has
        validated the signature content, the protocol is complete.
        </t>
    </section>

</middle>

<back>

</back>

</rfc>

